[Music]
are you ordering anything Twilight not
today I brought my own snack what I
thought you were treating me no I asked
if you wanted to come for lunch and this
is my
lunch you're going to eat a lunch Le
yeah haven't you heard about what
they've been saying about it on the
horse internet the cheese has molded
it's fine if cheese has a little bit of
mold I really don't think so does do
that even come with a Capri Sun it comes
with prime isn't lunchy for 8-year-olds
why the do Phillies need an energy
drink me in my soft pink I
can't get this sauce packet open does it
even have a tear line maybe it's just
hard as a to
[Music]
see that cheese is blue it's supposed to
be that
way nah
morning girly pops let's get those puss
popping hey Twilight is that a lunch
Le no no hey Rainbow Dash try on any new
dresses lately haahaha what no why would
you say something like
that yo Rainbow Dash a little pony told
me you used to dress in style is that
true you fancy ass little
oh my God sweet no Celestia no
there's no no way these could
have learned about my dark past I wish
to leave behind why are they saying
stuff like that everybody knows you walk
around naked and let it all hang out so
your lady bits Can Be Touched by the
cool air don't ask me you know I I I
hate clothes and fashion what an eternal
horse damnation is going on
here excuse me excuse me have you smelly
seen the blue horse anywhere
she's a fashion icon of the world born
and raised right here in Ponyville
Fashion Icon no that's Rainbow Dash well
at least it looks like her but Rainbow
Dash wouldn't be caught dead in a dress
that's impossible like every pony knows
Rainbow Dash always dresses in style are
you yeah a little bit okay
sorry I can't help you with the blue
horse but I do recognize Pinkie Pie over
there if you want to talk about her did
we like ask about Pinkie Pie not really
you should like go jump off of a really
tall build
Pony though smells like I
swear it didn't smell like this when we
used to live here honestly I'm glad we
left this dump well it is what
every pony from Ponyville does when they
start making above the minimum wage
which in Ponyville is only
75 Fair Point this trendy lopsided bull
cut did cost me $2,000 at the salon
yesterday God I think I stepped in more
horeshit sweet Celestia do these horses
just just like Drop logs wherever in
this town hey girls turn around and
don't look I got a poop I need to go to
I'll do it right here we can all do it
together okay let's see who can make the
biggest pile of
crap oh my God Rainbow Dash Pinkie Pie
we finally found you where have you been
you crazy horse
girls oh golly I don't believe it toara
and star song The Old Dan is back
together what brings you girls back home
well we were just passing through and
thought it would be nice to have a
little get together for Old Time sake I
hope it's not a bit too sudden um
Rainbow Dash who exactly are these two
20-year-old women oh right you wouldn't
know they were our buddies way before
you and the other girls came along that
there is toar Rola she's like the best
painter in all of Equestria I I mean
you've probably seen her work somewhere
without even realizing it she's just
that famous also her favorite food are
egg Tarts and she's also a
millionaire technically a
multi-billionaire but who's counting and
the one with the huge knockers is star
song She's this huge Idol famous all
over the country with fan clubs and
everything where people pay her to spit
on them Princess Celestia makes me spit
on her and I don't get so rainbow
how's your business coming along we
haven't heard heard a thing from you in
ages business Rainbow Dash's fashion
business it's only the most obvious
thing in the world it was clear from day
one that she was meant for greatness on
the runway when she would show up to our
picnics wearing giant hats well you know
I've been expanding my brand really
hitting the high fashion circuits so
where are you girls staying in Ponyville
I'm not asking so I can sneak into your
hotel room tonight and watch you sleep
he he and more importantly when are you
leaving
Tula Rula is having an Art Exhibit here
next week when we read about sugar cube
Corner's success in the paper we just
knew was the perfect excuse to come say
hi who would have thought one Little
Pony with a massive ass could make cakes
that rival Manhattan's finest what can I
say I know how to bake that's
incredible you little pink I'm
glad we all became millionaires because
it validates the whole reason we
interacted with each other
I guess greatness is drawn to Greatness
I'm a multibillionaire extra emphasis on
the multi-
part so pinky are you going to take us
to your cake shop or what uh how about
instead of going there we head on over
to Rainbow Dash's Boutique instead pinky
what the hell do you think you're doing
you know I don't own a boutique anymore
well figure it out you had so much time
to prepare for this moment why do you
think I opened my bakery in the fr first
place maybe it's time we come clean to
all our friends that I never made it as
a fashion designer and you never learned
how to bake and all of your cakes are
imported from Manhattan and selling them
at a 200% up charge no way my lie is
still holding up you're the one who
failed to cover Your Tracks better hold
up Pinkie Pie you don't know how to bake
and Rainbow Dash you knew about this do
the rest of our friends know about this
there's a lot you don't know honey do
you know cherly is sco's sister
what know that's that can't be true
don't ask questions if you're not
prepared for the answer let's go
dashy Rarity what are you doing here I'm
standing in the middle of my own living
room why are you entering my house
Uninvited get the hell out of my
house get that wh yeah get her Rainbow
Dash Rainbow Dash more like eat my ass
dang Twilight Sparkle do your friends do
this all the time not all the
[Music]
time rainbow why is there a baby in your
closet
uh I'm a pedophile close the door and
lock it back we're so proud of you for
being honest Rainbow Dash I bet that
must be hard to talk about how do you
even afford such a place I bet it must
cost you a fortune we can't that's why
Rarity is going to lose it we've gone
bankrupt so are you going to show us
around the place wasn't planning on it
then why are we here whatever let's just
go to sugar cube corner so Pinkie Pie
can show us how she makes her iconic
cakes yeah it's weird how she makes
cakes when her name is pie uh how about
instead of doing that we go to the
museum and check out toa's awesome art
instead good the art museum I
haven't been there in quite some time
probably since my mom and dad took me
when I was just a little Philly um we
didn't ask you that I know I just wanted
to share that little detail so that we
could become closer friends Twilight
this is our friend group not
[Music]
yours hey do you girls remember that one
winter wishes Festival where Pinkie Pie
tried practicing how to do a
wish and she thought that if she yelled
really loud it would make the
wish come
faster oh oh my gosh don't remind me
that was so embarrassing holy I
totally forgot about that what's so
funny you wouldn't get it you weren't
there hey walking Hot Topic ad go to the
concession stand and buy us some
strawberry lemonade tula roua and I are
getting like super
thirsty shouldn't you be the ones
treating us you two said you were
millionaires no I said I was a
billionaire
well anyway there's five of us and I
only have enough bits for four
lemonades that's fine you don't need to
have one this is my latest piece the
museum bought it off of me for 7 million
bits that's so cool to Rula or should we
say 20% cooler 20% cooler than what oh
that's that's just a thing I started
saying well you should
stop do you know why this painting uses
only the color yellow it's because I did
it with my
piss uh oh really now the process is one
that I invented myself where I pee all
over the canvas let it age a bit
so it turns a muddy yellow brown color
and then I piss all over the canvas
again to do the lighter tones then I dip
the final product in resin to keep the
colors to my
liking so you pee and the museum
buys this stuff off of you I've grown
Beyond paint now now most of my
paintings involve piss do you like have
a pea
fetish no she just has a fetish for
creation yeah that's all it is give me
four
lemonades why is everything going
wrong today
wow is this Tara's painting it's so
pretty the Exquisite Singularity and
application of just one color invites an
almost synesthetic depth imbuing the
piece with a warmth that transcends mere
chromatic selection wait where are you
all going I want to look around the
museum some more don't worry about it I
don't want you looking at my art anyway
it's obvious by looking at the uneven
streaks of tacky colored hair dye in
your man that you don't really have the
eye for art anyway H it's true what
would she know about art the reads
books without pictures well don't forget
your lemon Aid at least hydration is
important oh my God Twilight stop you're
being extra annoying today come on it's
about time we head over to sugar cube
corner to see what pinky is working with
uh how about instead of doing that we go
to the outside music venue instead that
sounds like a plan
I need to prepare for the concert I will
be performing there in the evening
anyway because I'm famous as
holy look out the turnout is
it usually this
packed there are two horses here that's
twice as many as last time it's no
wonder why you're so rich Star song I
sell my tickets for $7 a piece which
means with this many ponies I am going
to get4 Whole dollars I'd better get up
on stage the show starts in 57 minutes
we'll be sitting in the front row as
long as those seats aren't already taken
by my adoring fans they're not there's
only two other ponies
[Music]
here this is the first time I'm walking
away from
[Music]
you but this is a third
time you broke
something from you where are you going
you said this is your friend you haven't
seen in a long time I'm out I
can't just sit here and watch Star song
be a successful
millionaire not when I'm just a failure
at
everything now baby girl you are not a
failure yes she is I'm going to go to I
have to head back to Sugar CBE corner to
unload my main hat and cakes I need to
bake my homemade cakes
[Music]
evening GP what can I help you with
today Darlings Tula Rula wants a pastel
scarf for the Fall Festival make that
something
fabulous what a little and a
if you ask me I think she looks just
dashing enough already but I'll see what
I can
do oh my goodness oh my goodness
[Music]
I'm back Darlings what do you think
doesn't it just look stunning it's kind
of expensive but this is exactly what I
wanted thank me after you pay me rainbow
really knows how to make clothes up in
this this is the only good piece
of clothing she has made in in the past
year it's so good it's almost like this
lesbian didn't make
it it's so good it's almost like this
lesbian didn't make it
[Music]
whoa is this that one hot air balloon we
flew around and during that one twinkle
wish Adventure what is a twinkle wish
why do you keep saying that the very
same I bought it from the pawn shop
after pinky pawned it there for a bag of
mints why don't you climb a board for
Old Time sake oh boy would I you know if
you want to you could always come with
us thanks for the offer girls but we are
you for real that' be awesome but rain
what about Twilight and the girls you
can always write letters don't be a lame
yeah I also got this one highrise
apartment in Las Pegasus collecting dust
you could totally have it if you want
you'd love the view you hear that pinky
a high-rise apartment but I'm scared of
heights what about Applejack and
Fluttershy who's
Fluttershy pinky these two were
our friends first if you want to go I
won't stop you I'm mean you always
wanted to explore more I just hoped that
exploring was in my ass but if you
really want cool beans see you
I'll call you when I get to my awesome
skyrise apartment if I don't it'll
probably because I got a new phone since
I got a lot of
money
woohoo hey Twilight have you seen
Rainbow Dash she owes me
$12 she's gone Apple Jack she's gone
what where did she go she's just gone
what do you mean she's just gone is she
okay she left with Tara And Star song
who the is tulaa that name sounds
like a breakfast cereal I don't want to
hear that from anyone named Apple Jack
so much for the element of loyalty even
if she changes her mind in a week I
still think we should revoke her
position as the element of loyalty and
give it to me so that I can have two of
them Fluttershy stopped treating The
Elements of Harmony like Girl Scout
badges well why can't I why do you get
the element of magic because I can use
magic but Rarity can also use magic why
can't she also have it because that's
not how it works well it should be I can
see why Rainbow Dash didn't call to say
goodbye to
[Music]
you poor Pinkie Pie she looks so
sad you could always come visit her when
you want I guess you're right and even
if it's not how we hoped and all of her
cakes are imported from Main hat in it's
good to know she's financially stable
wait you mean you knew this whole time I
guess The Jig Is up for me too then that
Boutique I showed you wasn't really mine
it belonged to my friend Rarity and the
little girl in the closet was her sister
I'm not really a pedophile that's good
we don't need two pedophiles in this hot
air balloon
haha but there's three of us wait are
one of you
uh the time I'm walking
away from
you but this is a third
time you broke
[Music]
something from you don't
cry
I myself this is all in my
head don't
cry I keep tell myself you will wake up
instead
[Music]
don't
cry down
[Music]
[Applause]
this is the first time I'm
[Music]
walking from
you thanks again for letting me hang out
with you girls this is all I've ever
wanted hey it's no sweat you know we've
always loved you girl who wants to play
the Candyland board game next that
sounds fun I really like Candy Land
because it has lots of colors Derpy
you're supposed to say no like Rainbow
Dash always did I'm starting to think
you're only letting me hang out with you
as a replacement for Rainbow Dash and
you know what I'm fine with
it Rainbow Dash dashy you girls didn't
really think I would leave you behind in
this stain that is Ponyville all
alone did
you Derpy you can go home now your
usefulness has come to an end what are
you pulling out Candyland I love
that pull out a seat for me
too Applejack Rarity you to can
go home too why us you know we only like
hanging out in groups of
six come on Rarity let's go before she
eats
us do you want to come hang out at my
house and eat popcorn I have one of
those metal popcorn tins they sell
around Christmas time that's split into
three sections with normal popcorn
caramel popcorn and the cheddar cheese
flavored kind that nobody ever eats I
bet the three of us could finish off the
rest of it I don't like cheddar popcorn
that's why I brought it up I need to get
rid of it no offense Burpy but I'd
rather kill myself than hang out with
you any longer looking at your eyes kind
of gross me out I'm sure you understand
I I don't I don't look at my own face
that often because I struggle to look at
myself in the mirror damn if that's how
it's like for you imagine how shitty it
is for us